♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Peter, come on, time to get dressed
for our Valentine's Day dinner.
We don't want to be late
for our reservation.
Reservation?
Yeah. I decided we're going
someplace nice this time.
Not like last year when we went
to the Outback Steakhouse,
but it's "out" as in the gay way.
We'll get to the specials,
but first, I need to tell you...
I'm gay.
The hell you are!
No waiter of mine is gonna be gay!
Peter, please. He's our waiter.
He's the only waiter we have.
Lois, our waiter is dead to us.
We have to focus all our
attention on our hostess now.
He-he just needs a little time.
Scott...
I'm finally ready to hear the specials.
Well, happy Valentine's Day, Lois.
Let's have a dying marriage
side-face kiss.
Mwah.
Well, I better set out
a can of tuna fish and a cigar
for Arthur Valentine.
I can't wait to see what he brings me.
Uh, you want to tell us
what the holy hell that was?
I'm afraid it's something we made up
that we finally need to deal with.
You see, years ago,
when Chris was in preschool...
Peter, poor Chris didn't get
a single valentine today
from any of his classmates.
What? Why not?
Apparently, he's not well liked.
Some of the kids think he's weird
because he takes his shirt off to pee.
Yeah, I taught him that.
That's also called "peeing."
Pee? Pee now?
No. No, Chris.
Why no valentines?
Hey, hey, hey, stop crying, Chris.
Y-You're gonna...
Y-You're gonna get tons of valentines.
I am? From who?
Um, from... Arthur Valentine.
R-Really?
Yeah, yeah, that's right!
Who's Arthur Valentine?
Only the most magical man ever.
And he comes every
Valentine's Day on-on a-a...
a purple Vespa to, um...
to bring candy and sweet notes
to children
who've managed to not use
any swears in the last year.
He does?
Uh-huh, and he has a long beard...
Oh, and-and he's got an eye patch.
B-But not for medical reasons,
he just likes the look.
Plus, he-he wears a Cat in the Hat hat
and sometimes a scarf,
no matter what Lois says
because it gives him a youthful vibe
and adds some color to his face.
We were just trying to cheer Chris up.
I assumed he'd outgrow it
in a few years,
but, Peter, it's time
we have a talk with Chris.
We've got to put an end to this
Arthur Valentine nonsense.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well, I best be going anyway.
Donna and I are spending
our Valentine's Day
in Johnnie Cochran pajamas,
just caressing each other
in a very beige bedroom.
Yeah, and hopefully Bonnie and I'll
do a sexy bath night like last year.
It was amazing.
She laid out a trail of rose petals,
and I elbow-crawled
to the sponge and shower chair.
I go down to the video store
and put my hand on Love Actually
at the same time as a woman, and I go,
"Oh, ho, ho, ho!
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!"
What about you, Brian? What are
your plans for Valentine's Day?
What? Oh, uh, no real plans, I guess.
Ha! Looks like Brian's the only
guy with nothing going on.
Hey, you can come over
to my house, Brian.
I thought you had
that whole thing with Bonnie.
I do, but she needs help lifting
me into the shower chair.
Good evening. I'm Tom Tucker.
Our top story, today
the Quahog River was dyed red
in honor of Valentine's Day.
So if you're looking
to do a river murder,
this could be your window.
Stupid Hallmark holiday anyway.
Oh, hey, Bri. How's your night going?
I hope Rupert and I haven't been
too loud up there.
Happy Valentine's Day!
Oh, yeah, we're gonna go all night.
Just leave me alone, Stewie.
Well, Brian, if you're stuck
being a single loser,
you might as well just embrace it.
Mmm. Oh, yeah.
Wait a minute. What am I thinking?
Chocolate is poisonous to dogs.
I better stop or...
Happy Valentine's Day!
Stop the damn banging!
People are trying to have
dignified relations!
Oh, boy, look!
Arthur Valentine brought me
plates and a salt shaker!
Chris, Chris, settle down.
I-It's actually time your father and I
had a talk with you
about Arthur Valentine.
Yeah, that's, uh, that's right.
Um, son...
I'm afraid Arthur Valentine isn't real.
What? Not real?
Then who leaves those notes
with all the misspellings?
Well, first, Chris, English
is a very fluid language.
We're sorry, but you're old
enough now to know the truth.
He... he doesn't exist.
No! You're both lying!
What are we gonna do?
It seems like there's
no getting through to him.
You know, if Chris
is this hard to convince,
we may just have to kill
Arthur Valentine.
What? What do you mean?
Maybe we make Chris believe
that Arthur Valentine is dead.
Huh. Well, we just might have to.
Hey, what's the matter, Brian?
Have you fallen and can't get up?
Turns out, still using
that joke is a felony.
Guess I better not drop the soap.
That one's the death penalty.
You were very lucky.
We managed to pump your stomach
just in time.
Oh, thank God.
I had him pump my stomach, too.
Doc, what was in there?
Well, it's a pretty extensive list.
I'm gonna need Billy Joel
to help me out.
♪ Lots of Legos, rubber bands,
web-shooting Spider-Man ♪
♪ An old pet rock, an antique
clock, a ton of red Play-Doh ♪
♪ Colored pencils, lots of nickels ♪
♪ Half a jar of Vlasic Pickles ♪
♪ Banjo strings, chicken wings,
Cassingle by Skee-Lo ♪
♪ I didn't poop those items
♪ They were in my tummy
'cause they all looked yummy ♪
♪ He didn't poop those items ♪
♪ He tried to eat 'em,
so you shouldn't feed him. ♪
Wow, that was great, Billy!
Hey, does anyone call you
Bill Joel or William Joel?
Uh, no. Does anyone call you
Petey Griffin?
No, they don't, because I'm an adult,
which is kind of what I was getting at.
Ugh. Who sends a Christmas card
to their vet?
I know. It's so lame, right?
And did you see the lady outside
with the empty cat carrier?
Ugh. Cry much?
Yeah. Yeah, I bet she actually
thinks that thing loved her.
Hey, I'm Brian.
Shake.
Nice to meet you. I'm Ellie.
What are you in for?
Uh, I got this small cut,
and they wanted to bandage it
so I'd stop chewing
the crap out of my foot.
Aw, that sucks. I love chewing
I know, it's the best.
But while I was here,
I also had to get...
a prescription filled.
Listen, I got to go.
You want to continue this sometime?
Let me give you my number.
It's on the back of here.
- It's this.
- Got it.
See you around, Brian.
Definitely.
Bye, Ellie.
Is this the Veteran Aryan's office?
No, this is the veterinarian's.
I think you want the Veteran
Aryan's Center next door.
Ah, I see the confusion.
This must happen all the time.
We're ready for the German shepherd.
Ja, that would be me.
This is a very confusing lobby.
Hey. Hey.
You think you could be with me?
Right here? In this place?
Oh, yeah, yeah, sorry. Sorry, Stewie.
It's-it's just...
I met someone amazing the other
day at the vet's office, and...
Well, she's actually a dog.
And it's so great dating someone
who understands
why it's especially important
to walk around in a circle
many, many times before lying down.
So, that's who you were texting with?
Sort of. I-I was just rereading
some of the texts
I already sent her.
That's good.
You're rereading your own texts?
Yeah, do you, do you not do that?
Nobody does that.
Golden Eagle to Red Shrew.
Ready for the plan?
Come in, Red Shrew.
Peter, we did not decide on those names.
Chris, come down here, quick!
I see Arthur Valentine outside!
I think he's come to say hi!
Really?!
Yeah, look.
Oh, my God. Hi, Arthur!
I love you so much,
and I haven't cussed once today!
Dad, get the bowl of tuna
from under my bed!
Arthur!
Oh, my God, he's dead.
He's dead!
Mission accomplished, Red Shrew.
Over and out.
Huh. That looks tasty.
Little walkie-talkie piece.
God, I forgot how much I love art.
Hey, who's your favorite artist?
Me? Uh...
You know, I really like,
uh, that Jackson "Polack."
You know, I-I know they're not
supposed to be that bright,
but that was, that was
pretty genius, you know?
I mean, leave it, leave it to
a Polack to just grab the paint
with his hands and just start
chucking it everywhere.
I mean, it's great.
It's pronounced "Pollock."
But, Brian, you don't
have to keep trying so hard
to impress me.
I already really like you.
You do? Thanks.
I-I really like you, too, Ellie.
Truth is, I haven't felt this
way with anyone in a long time.
Listen, I'm really sorry
to cut things short,
but I've got to go; I have rehearsal.
- Oh, what, for a play?
- No.
It's kind of dumb,
but it's for a dog show.
Oh, you're a show dog?
No wonder you have
such a perfectly coiffed anus.
Thank you.
No, thank you. It's perfect.
I mean, I... God, I-I bet every
time you go snaffling on it,
you have to stop and admire it.
Come on, now, Brian.
A lady has to have a few secrets.
Man, she is something else.
This must be how Ronald Reagan
felt about Nancy.
Nancy, will you make me
the happiest man in the world
by turning a blind eye
to the AIDS crisis
and ineffectually trying to warn
young people about drugs?
Yes!
Oh, yes, Ronnie! Yes!
♪ If you're too young ♪
♪ Those are both things she did! ♪
Peter, I'm really worried about Chris.
The shock of seeing Arthur Valentine die
seems to have really gotten to him.
I-I've never seen him
so depressed and catatonic.
Well, you know, in Awakenings,
Robin Williams tossed a baseball
to Robert De Niro,
and he snapped out of it and caught it.
M-Maybe we do that.
Chris, you doing okay?
It's Mom and Dad.
We thought we'd... Awakenings!
Peter, I'm not sure that's...
Awakenings!
You're gonna hurt him if you...
Peter, knock it off.
I never thought Chris would
take things so hard.
I think we went too far
by killing Arthur Valentine.
We have to bring him back to life.
What? Are you serious?
It's the only thing
that'll snap him out of it.
Well, maybe, but what if
I try it with a basketball?
Awakenings!
Oh, God, that broke his nose.
He didn't even flinch.
It's bad. Let's do your thing.
Let's-let's twirl some
toilet paper up into his nose,
and-and then when...
we'll-we'll do your thing.
Wow, thanks again.
What a nice dinner.
I'm so lucky to have met you, Brian.
You're such an amazing guy.
I'd say we're both lucky.
Oh, no, no, no, wait!
Don't-don't do that.
What-what? What's the matter?
Oh, brutal.
Yeah, that's gonna be
a terrible car ride, man.
I would hate to be you, and I'm me.
I'm really sorry, Brian.
It's not that I don't want to kiss you.
I smell the poop on your breath,
and then that's all I want,
but my owners made an arrangement
with the organizers
of the next dog show.
They paid a lot of money
to schedule me to breed
with whichever male dog
wins the competition.
What, like... like breed breed?
I know it might seem odd to you,
but this happens in the dog show world.
I have to have sex with
whichever male dog wins,
whoever that ends up being.
Stewie, we're entering a dog show!
- Where's Stewie?
- He ate me!
- I ate him.
- ♪ He ate Stewie, holy crap ♪
♪ Family Guy will be right back! ♪
All right Brian,
now if we're going to get you
ready to compete in that dog show,
we've got a lot of training to cover.
Let's begin by doing
some work with the clicker.
Oh, yeah, I've seen these.
You click it when
you want me to do a trick,
and then I get a treat,
so I associate the two.
No. I use it to punctuate my jokes.
Now, Brian you've got to roll
over and be good on all fours.
If Nathan Lane can do it, so can you.
Okay.
But maybe we should just focus
on getting ready for the show.
Well, look who wants to be prepared.
You're a regular Beagle Scout.
Wait, shouldn't I be the one
who clicks if I like the joke?
You can't just click
after everything you say.
If it's funny, I can.
And so far, they've all landed.
Unlike the planes on 9/11.
See? No click.
That one was in poor taste. Not funny.
You know, I was supposed to be
on one of those planes.
Yeah, me, too.
Um, yes. Brian Griffin.
Brian?
What are you doing here?
Oh, hey!
Uh, you know, I...
You-you just made dog shows
sound so fun the other day,
I-I thought I'd give it a try.
Who knows? Maybe I'll end up top dog.
And on top of you.
Thanks, Stewie.
Brian, most of these dogs
have been training since birth.
Are you sure you're ready for this?
You bet I am.
I've never been so prepared.
I'm a regular Beagle Scout.
That's hilarious.
Good luck, Brian.
Chris, you got to snap out of this.
I mean, I've been where you're at.
Listen, I've never told anyone this,
but I killed a jaywalker in 2002.
She looked old, but she was only 51.
I mean, back then, that was old to me.
It's why I always talk
and ask questions so much.
When there's any moment
of quiet, I think about her.
That's why all mothers do that.
Every mother has killed someone.
Now drink your ginger ale.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's Arthur Valentine,
here to accelerate awkwardly
into a bush.
Damn it!
Arthur...
Valentine?
Chris! You're okay!
But I saw him die.
That can only mean one thing.
He must be a zombie!
What? No! No, no. What?!
Stop!
What the hell are you doing?!
I've seen The Walking Dead!
I have to destroy your brain
and then talk about it
for the next hour!
- Chris, take it easy!
- Get off of him!
- You're gonna kill me!
- It's not what you think!
Dad?
But... I don't...
I... How did...
I'm not Arthur Valentine, son.
We're so sorry, Chris.
Now do you understand?
There is no Arthur Valentine?
We never meant to hurt you, buddy.
Valentine's Day would
take on new meaning for Chris
in the years to come,
but he would remember none
so bittersweetly as this one.
This is Joe Swanson, signing off.
Joe, your mom died.
Seriously?
How you doing? You feeling good?
Because this thing is gonna
come down to the arbitrary whims
of whatever elderly volunteers
were able to get transportation
here on a Tuesday.
Yeah, I... Hey, watch it!
The hell's his problem?
Careful. That's your competition.
His name's Max.
He's a four-time winner
and kind of a crowd favorite.
Okay, who wants to start the dog show?
Who wants to start it?
Yes, you all want to start
the dog show, don't you?
Don't you?
♪
That'll do it for the males.
And as our judges tabulate the results,
we can now announce our female division.
The winning bitch,
for the tenth year in a row,
is Katherine Heigl!
Thank you, thank you.
No, but for real,
it's that dog Ellie over there.
And our winner
in the male division is...
Brian Griffin!
Yes!
Man, thank you for
all your help, Stewie.
I really couldn't have done it...
What the... What's going on?
This-this is it?
It's happening right here? Right now?
Uh-huh. They have to certify
the union, Brian.
Stud is ready to mount.
Please turn up the lights.
What? No! No, the opposite!
In fact, could someone maybe turn on
some-some Drake or The Weekend?
Ha! He's blowing it! He can't do it!
Quagmire?! What are you doing here?
Oh, I have an all-access pass
to anything in this town
that's sex-related.
Offering manual assistance.
Commencing union.
Okay, okay, thanks, man, but, yeah, no,
I-I got this, I got this.
If-if you just-just give me
a second to get, like,
a scenario in my head.
Uh, maybe a hot babysitter
who needs to pay for college
so she, uh...
Can somebody please shut those dogs up?!
This specimen is unable to perform.
Please bring in the boxer.
I'm sorry, Brian, but this is
what I was trying to tell you.
I'm sorry, too, but I see now
that you were right.
I'm just not sure how this could work
or-or how our relationship
could fit into your world.
Hey, less talk!
I guess this is good-bye.
I guess it is.
I'll always remember you, Brian.
And I'll always remember you, Ellie.
I promise to name
one of the puppies after you.
Let's just cross our fingers...
it's not one of the ones he eats.
Thanks. That means a lot...
Okay, we're at the part
where he bites down
on the back of my neck, so we
should probably wrap this up.
Yup.
Whoa! Max's grandfather
may have been a horse.
Come on, let's just go home.
Okay.
Is this the romantic ending
you were hoping for?
Look, that was a tricky
situation, all right?
The lights, the people watching.
If-if it hadn't been for all that, I...
trust me, I-I would've, I
would've set her world on fire.
No way. You didn't even start the fire.
Oh, no.
♪ Nancy Reagan, preschool Chris ♪
♪ Sey valet, young Lois ♪
♪ German guy, lots of dogs ♪
♪ Arthur Valentine ♪
♪ We didn't write an ending ♪
♪ So we're all together,
trying to make it better ♪
♪ They didn't write an ending ♪
♪ But what the heck?
I'll still take the check ♪
♪ The check, the check. ♪
Mom killed a jaywalker.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru